<!DOCTYPE html><html><head>
<title>Terms of Service</title>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0">
<link href="/.static/css/global.css" type="text/css" rel="stylesheet">
  <meta name="description" content="8chan is an infinitely-expanding imageboard for any community. Whether you’re into obscure hobbies, games, or random interests, 8chan’s got a spot for you. It's a place to share, chat, and discover cool stuff with people who are into the same things—no matter how unique. Jump in and be part of something that’s always growing and evolving.">
</head>
<body>
  <header>
    <img src="/.static/logo.png" class="logoImg" alt="logo">
  </header>

  <div class="titleWrapper">
    <fieldset class="titleFieldset">
      <legend>Terms of Service</legend>
        <h1>Welcome to 8chan!~moe</h1>
        <hr>
        <p>
        8chan is an infinitely-expanding imageboard for any community. Whether you’re into obscure hobbies, games, or random interests, 8chan’s got a spot for you. It's a place to share, chat, and discover cool stuff with people who are into the same things—no matter how unique. Jump in and be part of something that’s always growing and evolving.
        </p>
        <p>
        </p><h2>You must agree to follow all site rules:</h2>
        <p></p>
        <ol start="0">
          <li>Exceptional situations may justify exceptional solutions.</li>
          <li>Users are forbidden from posting, receiving, or transmitting content that is illegal under applicable laws. This site does not provide a platform for illegal activity of any kind.</li>
          <li>Images or any other kind of media depicting the sexual abuse of real children is explicitly forbidden and will be reported to law enforcement. Additionally "jailbait" and other borderline content are prohibited. This content is defined as:
          <ol type="a">
            <li>Any depiction of a real child regardless of original context, legality, or public display, that is posted in any sort of context that is sexualized, sexually suggestive, or otherwise intended to elicit arousal.</li>
            <li>Realistic art or 3DCG images based on real children that are sexualized as per above.</li>
          </ol></li>
          All depictions of fictitious characters are 18+ years of age regardless of any contradicting textual description(s). Legal, fictional 2D or 3DCG artwork is not prohibited and is not to be conflated with pedophilia or any content banned under this rule.
           <li>Board Ownership and User Accounts are granted and maintained at the discretion of the site administration. Severe abuse, neglect, or mishandling of your board, its rules, or its users may result in its loss or reassignment.</li>
           <li>Users are prohibited from any activity, including the use of third party tools or scripts, that damages the site or its functions. This includes but is not limited to spamming, flooding, phishing, psyops, hacking, denial of service and other attacks, and bot programs or other unauthorized software.</li>
           <li>You must be 18 years of age or older to browse this website.</li>
           <li>Do not post NSFW material on SFW marked boards unless it is spoilered.</li>
         </ol>
         <h2>Disclaimer and Terms of Service</h2>
         <p>This site and its administration claim no responsibility for what users post to our platform. Pursuant to US Law we make a good-faith effort to remove content which we believe in good faith to be unlawful. No individual may use our site to post content in violation of applicable laws, especially those of the United States of America. By browsing this site you agree to accept any and all risks to your computer, data, and self, you agree to abide by the Global Rules of the site, and you further agree to hold harmless and indemnify all service providers, partners, staff, owners, administration, and volunteers of this site to the greatest possible extent permitted under law for any and all content that you create, post, share, experience, download, execute, or are otherwise exposed to.
         <br>
         </p><h1><a href="/.static/pages/confirmed.html">I AGREE AND WISH TO PROCEED</a></h1><a href="/.static/pages/confirmed.html">
         <p></p>

    </a></fieldset><a href="/.static/pages/confirmed.html">
  </a></div><a href="/.static/pages/confirmed.html">


</a></body></html>