<!doctype html>
<html lang="en">
<title>This website is not available in Arizona, US</title>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width, initial-scale=1" />

<style>
    * {
        margin: 0;
        padding: 0;
        box-sizing: border-box;
    }

    html {
        font-family: 'sans-serif';
        background-color: black;
    }

    body {
        padding: 32px;
        margin: 144px auto 10px auto;
        max-width: 700px;
        background-color: deeppink;
        border-radius: 16px;
        box-shadow: 0 0 64px deeppink;

        transition: padding 100ms;
        transition: margin 100ms;


        & > h1 {
            display: block;
            margin-bottom: 32px;
            color: #530101;
        }

        & > main > div#lawinfo {
            & > div {
                display: table-row;

                & > * {
                    padding: 0 4px;
                    display: table-cell;
                }
            }
        }
    }

    @media only screen and (max-width: 480px) {
        body {
            padding: 0;
            padding-bottom: 16px;
            margin: 0;

            & > h1 {
                padding: 32px;
                padding-bottom: 0px;
                margin-bottom: 0px;
            }

            & > main {
                margin: 0 12px;
            }
        }
    }
</style>
<body>
<h1>This website is not available in Arizona, US</h1>
<main>
    <h2>What?</h2>
    <p>The server has detected you live in Arizona (US). This jurisdiction puts legal requirements on
        websites containing adult material to block access entirely, verify ID, track age verification, and/or keep
        records for a long period of time.</p>
    <p>At this moment, this website does not implement the legally mandated verification mechanisms to permit you access
        to its content, if such content is permissible for you to view at all.</p>

    <h3>Huh?</h3>
    <p>The type of block encountered: <strong>privacy-infringing age verification methods</strong>. Consult the legal information linked below for
    a more detailed explanation.</p>

    <h2>Details</h2>
    <div id="lawinfo">
        <div>
            <span>Law name</span><span>Arizona HB 2112</span>
        </div>
        <div>
            <span>More information</span><span><a href="https://legiscan.com/AZ/text/HB2112/id/3239821" rel="noopener">https://legiscan.com/AZ/text/HB2112/id/3239821</a></span>
        </div>
    </div>

    <h2>What can I do?</h2>
    <p>This website is not planning on adding new age verification methods any time soon, so there is not much you can
        do. Consider voting for politicians that oppose laws like <em>Arizona HB 2112</em> in the future so measures
        like these are no longer necessary.</p>
    <p>If your government does not permit access to adult content at all, despite age verification methods, this website
    will not be accessible to you.</p>
    <p>Note that bypassing legal blockades may be a criminal offence. Check with your local laws and regulations before
    attempting to bypass legal content restrictions. This website will not take responsibility for attempts to bypass
    legal restrictions.</p>
</main>
